# Mauro Polino

GitHub | in LinkedIn | ⊕ mauropolino.com | ≥ mchumpitazp@gmail.com | -51 901-444-236

# SUMMARY

I am an electronics engineer and full-stack web developer. I worked in a tech company, within a five person team, developing hardware and software solutions for mid and large projects where my soft skills were tested and improved as a team member. My main tech stack includes databases, React, Node and Microsoft Azure. On top of that, my major field is front-end with React Hooks, Redux and Bootstrap 5.

## **EDUCATION**

2015 - 2021	University of Engineering and Technology - UTEC Bachelor's degree in Electronics Engineering
2022	Harvard University Certified in Web Programming with Python and JavaScript
2022	The Hong Kong University of Science and Technology Certified in Full-Stack Web Development with React
2023	IELTS General Training 7.5/9 - CEFR Level C1 (Advanced)

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

### CITA - Water Technology and Research Center - Tech Developer

Sep 2020 - Nov 2021

#### Recomendation Letter

- Built embedded and Internet of Things systems for non-invasive data measurements required from rivers in Peru for post application of Large Scale Particle Image Velocimetry algorithm.
- Manufacturated electronics and designed a web front-end and databases, following Scrum methodology, for a low-cost water monitoring system which was deployed by a peruvian government sanitation entity.

#### Freelancer Full-Stack Web Developer

Dec 2022 - Present

#### **Projects**

 Developed and deployed the client and server sides, including databases, of multiple websites for different companies around the world. These projects led me to improve my tech skills for real-life situations.

#### Main Projects

# Business Page using MERN Stack

URL 2023

Developed a business website for an esthetic company. Besides presenting information and products, the user interface includes attractive features as background overlaps, visual effects and interactive behaviour.

#### Landing Page linked to Azure SQL Database

URL 2023

Delivered a full-stack website which aims to display beauty products and attract new partners through a reliable form (with validation) whose data is stored in an external database for scalability.

#### SKILLS

Programming Javascript ES6, HTML5, CSS3, Python 3, C++, SQL

Tech Stack React, Redux, Bootstrap, Node, JQuery, OpenCV, Git, Microsoft Azure, MATLAB

Agiles Design Thinking, Scrum, Kanban

Languages Spanish (native), English (advanced), Russian (pre-intermediate)